# **Alexander Ulogov**

Full Stack PHP Developer

I am a Full Stack PHP Developer with more than fifteen years of hands-on experience. I have a strong background in web development and have worked on a wide range of projects from simple websites to complex web applications.

I am a self-motivated, hard-working, and goal-oriented person. I can work independently and as part of a team.

### **Experience**

 $\textbf{2003-2023} \cdot \mathsf{Self\text{-}Employed}$ 

Full Stack PHP Developer

- Discuss clients' business needs and develop custom web solutions.
- Develop and use my own framework.
- Work with web-designers.
- Maintain and update websites.
- Generate dynamic business and accounting reports.
- Search engine optimization.

#### 2007 – 2017 · Online Plumbing Store Mirsanteh

Full Stack PHP Developer

- Help to grow business from a small brick-and-mortar plumbing store to one of the top three Russian online plumbing stores.
- Build a very complex online store from the ground up.
- Build a module to exchange data with accounting software.
- Create dynamically generated business reports.
- Troubleshoot and resolve technical issues.
- Work with SEO and advertising agencies.

#### 2003 - 2006 · Online Toy Store Neopod

Full Stack Web Developer

- Develop a website for a small family toy store.
- Develop an accounting tool.
- Toy market research.
- Help to grow and sell the business.

#### **Education**

1996 – 2001 Moscow, Russia State University of Management Bachelor's degree, Financial Management

#### Contact

Jacksonville, Florida, US

+1 (334) 552-22-29

alulogov@gmail.com

www.alexu.dev

www.linkedin.com/in/aulogov

### **Skills**

Back-End:

PHP, MySQL, Python, Laravel, Flask

Front-End:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Vue

Additional:

SEO, MVC, JSON, XML, API, Git, LAMP

Deployment:

Digital Ocean, Linode, Ubuntu, Apache, Nginx

## Languages

English	
Russian	

### **Interests**

- Playing Soccer
- Woodworking
- Playing Chess